[Landlord 1] Come now sir, the polling starts soon
enough: you'll vote 'true blue' for the Old
cue-2
Interest sure?
[Farmer] Perhaps I will, perhaps I won't! We honest
cue-3
farmers always like to do what's in the
best interests of the country, so long as
cue-4
it aligns with my own interests of
course! … I will just say that I have heard
cue-5
the pie is very good at the inn you keep...
[Landlord 1] Aye, so it is, and the ale too.
cue-6
Here, take this here invitation to dine with
us. You shall have whatever you choose if
cue-7
you will but promise your vote.
[Landlord 2] Nay sir, you must come to eat at The
cue-8
Crown, yonder down the street. Our fare is
twice as good as his – and what's much
cue-9
better, you won't have to hold your nose
against the Old Interest stench! The
cue-10
Crown's where the New Interest resorts,
and we will treat you splendidly.
cue-11
[Farmer] Well … mayhap I may sup at both your inns.
But still I'm not
cue-12
decided. Is there aught more you could do
to help persuade me how to cast my
cue-13
vote?
[Landlord 1] Oh yes indeed. Here's silver, sir, to
cue-14
help you know your proper mind. Never let
it be said that we in the Old Interest don't know
cue-15
how to repay loyalty.
cue-16
[Farmer] Yes, loyal and honest, that's me to a T.
[Farmer to the other Landlord:] But tell me mister, what says the
cue-17
New Interest?
[Landlord 2] Only this, dear sir, that this gold guinea
cue-18
must eloquently explain why your support
should go to us.
cue-19
[Farmer to the audience] Their bribery has just begun. Why should I
pledge to either one? To each I'll give
cue-20
my separate oath, so of their bribes I
may take both!